Finding Aid for the Jack Hurst Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- O’Connor to Rankin
  - Dolly Parton, 10/2/76 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Dolly Parton, 3/26/89 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Dolly Parton, 5/10/91 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - (A) Dolly Parton – (B) Tex Ritter (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - J.P. Pennington @ MCA – 4/24/91 (of Exile) (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Minnie Pearl II (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Gretchen Peters, 6/21/96 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - (A) Michael Peterson 1/18/98 – (B) Jim Ed Norman 1/98 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Creator of Phantom of the Country Palace, 6/1/94 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Celinda Pink, 10/3/95 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - (A) Pinkard & Bowden (B) Deborah Allen (C) John Conlee (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Gary Presley, 5/18/91 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - (A) Kenny Price (& wife Donna) – (B)Lynn Gillespie & Jim Zumwalt (Nashville Pop) (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Ray Price, 5/05/98 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - (A) Glenda Faye 1988 – (B) John Prickland (Name unclear) – 2/13/88 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - (A) John Prine – 8/15/90 – (B) Vince Gill (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Eddie Rabbitt – 9/24/80 & Bill Rehrig (Eddie Rabbitt’s road manager) 9/23/80 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - (A) Eddie Rabbitt – 11/24/90 – (B) Tim DuBois & et al 7/16/90 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Eddie Rabbitt (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Rankin Family, early 1995 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- Rattlesnake Annie to Sharp
  - Rattlesnake Annie, 5/14/87 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Marty Raybon of Shenandoah, 1/27/88 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Collin Raye, 1/14 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Collin Raye, 6/9/94 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Collin Raye, 12/1/95 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Red Hot and County Interviews @ Ryman (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - (A) Jerry Reed – (B) Dick Curlesi (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - (A) Don Reid (Statler Brothers) – 5/16/79 – (B) Reba McEntire 5/21/79 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Mike Reid, 1/29/91 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Mike Reid, 1/10/96 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - (A) Restless Heart – 11/86 – (B) Wild Choir 11/86 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Rick Richards, 4/7/87 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Kim Richey, 1/25/96 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Kim Richey, 8/01/97 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Riders in the Sky, 1/23/89 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Riders in the Sky, 5/1/91 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Riders in the Sky, 10/8/92 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Diamond Rio, 5/8/91 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Jeannie C. Riley, 7/14/81 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Jason Ringenberg (Jason & the Scorchers), 5/3/87 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Steve Ripley, 11/01/94 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Tex Ritter (on way to Oak Ridge) (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Dave Robbins, 10/23/98 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - (A) Pig Robbins – 10/10/82 – (B) Loretta Lynn – 10/82 – (C) Ralph Emery (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Judy Rodman, 8/19/86 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Wild Rose, 1/3/90 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Mark Rothbaum, 10/13/81 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - (A) Mark Rothbaum (Conclusion) – (B) Justice Newton 10/15/85 (C) Keith Whitley 10/15/85 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Billy Joe Royal, 3/21/89 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - The Sanders (Vicki and Dale) – March 14, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Big Sandy, 3/5/98 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - (A) Molly Scheer, (B) Moe Bandy 2/20/91 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Dan Seals, 2/12/86 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Dan Seals, 2/9/89 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Dan Seals, 6/9/92 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Martie Seidel (Mcguire) (Of Dixie Chicks), 10/23/98 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Kevin Sharp, 10/31/96 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Shaver to Stuart
  - Billy Joe Shaver, 8/12/93 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Billy Joe Shaver, 7/12/96 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Bettye Shelton & Audrey Land, 11/30/95 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Ricky Van Shelton – Demo of song “Rosie” 1985 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Ricky Van Shelton, 4/5/88 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Ricky Van Shelton, 1/19/91 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Ricky Van Shelton, 12/29/92 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Ricky Shelton (Undated) (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Ricky Van Shelton (“basement music” – looks like a demo tape) (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Shenandoah, 4/19/89 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Shenandoah, 7/24/91 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Jean Shepard, 11/9/74 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Danny Shirley (of Confederate Railroad), 3/6/94 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Danny Shirley (of Confederate Railroad), 6/25/96 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Evelyn Shriver, 10/13/88 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Evelyn Shriver, 10/20/98 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Ricky Skaggs, 5/15/89 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - SKB Schuyler, Knobloch & Bickhardt, 7/13/88 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - SKO Schuyler, Knobloch & Overstreet, 10/1986 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Connie Smith (Undated) (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - (A) Rob Smith 5/5/93 – (B) Suzy Bogguss 5/7/93 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Jo-El Sonnier 4/7/88 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - J. D. Spangler, Cary O’Dell, Lynn Shults, Bud Schaetzle, Martin Fischer, Paul Corbin (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Karen Staley, 11/12/89 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Keith Stegall 3/6/96 & Dan Smit? (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Ray Stevens, 11/1992 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Ray Stevens, Buddy Kalb, and Rod Thompson, 12/9/94 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Larry Stewart (Restless Heart) 2/19/90 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Doug Stone & Susan Nadler 2/26/90 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Doug Stone, 4/3/91 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Doug Stone, 8/5/92 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - (A) George Strait 9/28/89 – (B) Marty Stuart (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - George Strait, 9/22/95 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Stan Strickland (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Marty Stuart, 9/19/91 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Marty Stuart, 11/25/92 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Marty Stuart, 3/30/94 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- Stuart to Twitty
  - (A) Marty Stuart (con’t.) – (B) Steve Earle 4/29/86 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Rollin “Oscar” Sullivan (of Lonzo & Oscar) (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - (A) Sweethearts of Rodeo – 3/11/86 – (B) Reba McEntire (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - (A) Sweethearts of Rodeo – 12/14/89 – (B) Paulette Carlson (of Hwy 101) (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Sweethearts of Rodeo, 4/6/84 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Tom T. Hall (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Karen Taylor-Good & Larry Smith (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - (A) Karen Taylor-Good – (B) Louise Mandrell 10/15/85 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - (A) Mel Tillis 10/17/82 – (B) Dan Aykrod 10/21,22/1982 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Pam Tillis, 1/3/91 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Pam Tillis, 2/6/92 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Pam Tillis, 2/17/93 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - (A) Pam Tillis – early 1994 – (B) Wynonna Judd press conference (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Pam Tillis, 10/7/94 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Pam Tillis, 12/95 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Pam Tillis, 3/30/99 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Aaron Tippin – early January 1991 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Trish Townsend, 3/15/96 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Merle Travis, 8/2/79 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Randy Travis, 4/3/86 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Randy Travis, 10/29/88 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Randy Travis, 2/92 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Randy Travis, 4/26/94 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Randy Travis, 7/31/96 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Randy Travis, 5/28/98 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - (A) Randy Travis – (B) Lib Hatcher (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Rick Trevino – early 1995 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Rick Trevino, 7/30/96 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Tony Trischka, 5/5/99 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Travis Tritt, 5/1/91 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Travis Tritt, 8/19/92 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Travis Tritt, 8/5/96 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - (A) Travis Tritt – 4/29/98 – (B) Tim McGraw 4/30/98 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Tanya Tucker, 8/86 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Shania Twain, 2/6/96 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Shania Twain, 12/22/97 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Conway Twitty, 9/5/76 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Conway Twitty, 4/12/90 (Box 14, Folder 38)
- Tyler to Womack
  - Dan Tyler, 10/31/96 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Ian Tyson, 5/17/94 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Keith Urban, 3/25/97 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - (A) Tony Villanueva (of Derailers) – 5/9/96 – (B) George Jones, Nancy Jones & Tom Carter 5/13/96 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Porter Wagoner, 10/6/70 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - (A) Porter Wagoner – (B) Ernest Tubb 2/13/79 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - (A) The Wagoneers (Monte Warden) 8/7/89 – (B) New Grass Revival 8/7/89 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Cindy Walker, 9/14/88 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Clay Walker, 3/1/94 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Steve Wallach & Billy Ray Cyrus 6/26/93 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Steve Wariner, 2/20/92 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - (A) Doc Watson – (B) Newgrass Revival (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Gene Watson, 2/15/89 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Irving Waugh (90 min) (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Kevin Welch, 9/13/90 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Lloyd Werner & Cheryl Daly re: Canadian TV situation – (B) Shaun Purdue 1994 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - (A) Lloyd Werner – 2/7/91 – (B) Paul Corbin 1/29/91 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - (A) Dottie West – 10/5/82 – (B) Lee Greenwood 12/13/82 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - (A) Shelly West – 6/15/83 – (B) John Lentz & Kerry O’Neil (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Steve West - (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Lari White – 2/5/96 (Tape Broken) (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Keith Whitley (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - John and Audrey Wiggins – summer of 1994 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Honey Wilds I/II (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - (A) Honey Wilds III – (B) Ben Smathers of the Stoney Mountain Cloggers (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Williams and Ree – early January of 1987 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Dan Williams, 10/22/90 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Don Williams, 11/14/90 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Hank Williams, Jr., 9/27/77 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Hank Williams, Jr., 10/13/87 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - (A) Hank Williams, Jr. – 9/4/88 – (B) Mickey Gilley 9/8/88 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Hank Williams, Jr. – 6/5/91 (or 97?) (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Hank Williams, Jr. (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Hank Williams III, 8/9/96 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - (A) Leona Williams – 5/9/83 – (B) Moe Bandy 6/8/83 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Hal Willis, 7/13/93 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Kelly Willis – early June of 1991 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Lee Ann Womack, 8/28/98 (Box 15, Folder 38)
- Jane Word to Zimmerman
  - (A) Jane Word (B) Patti Bereyso 1986 (Film making in Nashville) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Women in the Round, 3/30/89 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Michelle Wright, 2/17/93 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Tammy Wynette, 12/8/76 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - (A) Tammy Wynette – 11-4-78 – (B) Chet Atkins 11-28-78 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - (A) Tammy Wynette – 11/23/80 – (B) Jerry Reed 1/21/81 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Tammy Wynette, 8/11/87 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Trisha Yearwood, 9/11/92 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Trisha Yearwood, 8/96 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - (A) Trisha Yearwood – (B) Tony Coutney? 6/11/91 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Dwight Yoakam, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Dwight Yoakam, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Dwight Yoakam, 7/20/88 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Dwight Yoakam, 10/02/95 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Roy Zimmerman & Kenny Rhodes (The Foremen), 9/16/96; Note: After Zimmerman, there is an empty cassette case followed by 5 Unidentified/ Blank Tapes. (Box 16, Folder 15)